<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ManKind</string>
    <string name="q1_Title">Let me know you</string>
    <string name="q1_prefix">All questions are between the scale 0 – 4 with 0 being definitely disagree to 4 being definitely agree.</string>
    <string name="q1_1">1.Your partner is very controlling of you</string>
    <string name="q1_2">2.Your partner is jealous of your success</string>
    <string name="q1_3">3.When you make small mistakes, your partner gets very angry</string>
    <string name="q1_4">4.Your partner hates some of your characteristics</string>
    <string name="q1_5">5.You are sometimes very afraid of your partner</string>
    <string name="q1_6">6.You\'re terrified to tell your partner anything he or she doesn\'t approve of.</string>
    <string name="q1_7">7.Your partner lies to you very often.</string>
    <string name="q1_8">8.Your partner has blackmailed you for something</string>
    <string name="q1_9">9.Your partner has used violence against you</string>
    <string name="q1_10">10.Your partner is extremely addicted to a substance</string>
    <string name="q1_11">11.You are sure that you or anyone in your family has been hurt</string>
    <string name="q2_prefix">ManKind is with you in every step of the way in ending the abuse you are subjected to. Together, we will ensure that you are happy and free again! Please answer the questions as accurately as possible to show the most appropriate content to you.</string>
    <string name="q2_1">1.What age category do you belong to?</string>
    <string name="q2_2">2.Which gender does your partner associate themselves with?</string>
    <string name="q2_3">3.How long back did you observe the first signs of abuse?</string>
    <string name="q2_4">4.Have you ever been physically hit, burnt, beaten or bruised?</string>
    <string name="q2_5">5.Have you ever felt physically scared of your partner?</string>
    <string name="q2_6">6.Has your partner ever threatened to harm you?</string>
    <string name="q2_7">7.Do you think your partner is financially controlling? </string>
    <string name="q2_8">8.Do you ever get scared while discussing finances with your partner? </string>
    <string name="q2_9">9.Do you ever lie or have caught your partner lie while talking about money?</string>
    <string name="q2_10">10.Do you ever feel like you are mentally tortured or stuck? </string>
    <string name="q2_11">11.Do you often feel low around your partner?</string>
    <string name="q2_12">12.Do you ever think your partner is harassing you or blackmailing you?</string>
    <string name="q2_13">13.Do you have a kid or kids with your partner?</string>
    <string name="registration_title">ManKind Registration</string>
    <string name="password_check">Two password should be same!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Resource</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Curriculum</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Visualization</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">NavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="connection">lithe-style-241007:australia-southeast1:man-kind</string>
    <string name="email">Email:</string>
    <string name="password">Password:</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="curriculum">Curriculum</string>
    <string name="visualization">Visualization</string>
    <string name="visualize">Pleasse choose the resources to be visualized</string>
    <string name="impact_assistance">Impact/Assistance</string>
    <string name="the_assistance_male_recipients_receive_from_centrelink">The assistance male Recipients receive from Centrelink</string>
    <string name="remember_there_are_no_correct_or_wrong_answers_do_not_spend_too_much_time_on_any_statement">● Remember there are no correct or wrong answers. Do not spend too much time on any statement.</string>
    <string name="in_the_next_couple_of_pages_you_will_be_presented_with_a_a_series_of_statements_please_read_each_statement_and_select_a_level_between_0_and_4_which_indicates_how_much_the_statement_was_relevant_to_you_over_the_past_week">● In the next couple of pages, you will be presented with a a series of statements. Please read each statement and select a level between 0 and 4 which indicates how much the statement was relevant to you over the past week.</string>
    <string name="this_self_assessment_test_should_take_about_2_minutes_to_complete">This self-assessment test should take about 2 minutes to complete.</string>
    <string name="the_content_will_contain_but_not_limited_to_self_help_curriculum_essential_resources_data_visualisation_and_self_assessment_tools">● The content will contain but not limited to self-help curriculum, essential resources, data visualisation and self-assessment tools.</string>
    <string name="note_there_are_hundreds_of_other_known_domestic_violence_types_that_are_not_covered_here">Note: There are hundreds of other known domestic violence types that are not covered here.</string>
    <string name="we_will_aim_to_identify_the_kind_of_domestic_violence_your_are_subjected_to_and_take_into_your_account_your_factors_while_displaying_a_specially_curated_content">● We will aim to identify the kind of domestic violence your are subjected to and take into your account your factors while displaying a specially curated content.</string>
    <string name="you_will_be_shown_a_series_of_questions_choose_the_most_suitable_answer_according_to_your_situation">● You will be shown a series of questions. Choose the most suitable answer according to your situation.</string>
    <string name="now_that_you_have_a_fair_idea_of_you_situation_let_us_understand_you_better_to_help_you">Now that you have a fair idea of you situation, let us understand you better to help you.</string>
    <string name="instruction">Instruction</string>
    <string name="set_your_goal">Set your Goal:</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="show_completed_tasks">Show Completed tasks</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="tasks_completed">Tasks Completed:</string>
</resources>
